/* jshint esversion: 8 */
//Quiz Questions and Options array

const questionsArray = [{

        question: "What is the longest river in Ireland?",
        options: ["The Liffey", "The Corrib", "The Shannon", "The Lee"],
        correct: "The Shannon",
    },
    {
        question: "What animal did St Patrick drive out of Ireland ?",
        options: ["Spiders", "Snakes", "Dragons", "Bears"],
        correct: "Snakes",
    },
    {

        question: "What is the name of  Irelands Capital city?",
        options: ["Cork", "Galway", "Dublin", "Limerick"],
        correct: "Dublin",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the President of Ireland ?",
        options: ["Michael D Higgins", "Leo Varadkar", "Marty Morrissey", "Bono"],
        correct: "Michael D Higgins",
    },
    {

        question: "What is  Irelands smallest county?",
        options: ["Louth", "Armagh", "Clare", "Wexford"],
        correct: "Louth",
    },
    {
        question: "What musical instrument does Ireland have as one of its official symbols ?",
        options: ["Harp", "Piano", "Drums", "Fiddle"],
        correct: "Harp",
    },
    {

        question: "What does  “sláinte” mean?",
        options: ["Cheers", "Hello", "Good Luck", "Goodbye"],
        correct: "Cheers",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is commonly known in Ireland as “the black stuff”? ?",
        options: ["Guinness", "Sausages", "Coal", "Money"],
        correct: "Guinness",
    },
    {

        question: "Kissing the Blarney Stone is said to bestow which talent upon the one kissing the stone?",
        options: ["Gift of the gab", "Singing", " Riverdancing", "Knowledge"],
        correct: "Gift of the gab",
    },
    {
        question: "How many leaves does a shamrock have? ?",
        options: ["2", "4", "6", "3"],
        correct: "3",
    },

];